Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Audio-Visual Materials, 1
  - Subseries 1.06: Conceiving Ada, 1.06
    - Mix Print Master Reel 1-5; undated (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Print Master (Carton 68, Folder 1)
    - Selects Roll #11-16; 1997 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 72, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.07: Conspiracy of Silence, 1.07
    - [Kodachrome movies]; undated, [unidentified director/producer] (10 items), Film: Super 8; [unidentified element] (Carton 27, Folder 2)
    - Silence; 1991-08-21 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 27, Folder 3)
    - 16mm Transfer Reel #5; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 28, Folder 7)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 28, Folder 8)
    - [Legal Version - master edit]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min., 30 min.; 00:00:15:00; [unidentified] (Carton 28, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.08: Cut Piece, 1.08
    - Patrick Martin Magic; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 23, Folder 1)
    - Rapa Cut Piece; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 24, Folder 1)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 2)
    - [Cut Piece dubs]; 1993 (3 items), Video: VHS; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 24, Folder 3)
    - Jaglem; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 24, Folder 4)
    - Interview with Mona - Whitney; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 24, Folder 5)
    - Ruff 6311; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 24, Folder 6)
    - Janet Pick ups; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 24, Folder 7)
    - eyeglasses, Channel 1 only; 1993-02-16 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 1)
    - Moira & Whitney; 1992-12 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:14:00:00 (Carton 26, Folder 2)
    - Yoko; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 1:00:00:00; 1:00:00:00 (Carton 26, Folder 3)
    - Rapa Yoko; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 4)
    - Yoko #1; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 5)
    - Yoko #1-5; undated (9 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub (Carton 26, Folder 6)
    - Cut Piece French Title, German credits; 1993 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 26, Folder 7)
    - Component Dub, French Version, German Version; 1993 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 26, Folder 8)
    - German title, German credits; 1993 (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:15:00:00 (Carton 26, Folder 9)
    - German Version, No Voice-Over; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 26, Folder 10)
    - French & German Titles, German End Credits; 1993 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 11)
    - American version w/Whitney, Chadwick & Moira Roth; 1993 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 12)
    - Cut Piece, Proxemics, New Time; 1993 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 13)
    - Cut Piece with Moira Roth, Whitney [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 00:22:30:00 (Carton 26, Folder 14)
    - American version w/ Whitney Chadwick & Moira Roth; 1993 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:22:30:00 (Carton 26, Folder 15)
    - Yoko Camera 1; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 26, Folder 16)
    - Homage to Yoko Ono; 1993 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min.; 00:15:30:00 (Carton 26, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1.09: Deep Contact, 1.09
    - Lynn's Deep Contact Promo Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 1)
    - Lorna, Room; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 43, Folder 2)
    - Documentation of "Deep Contact" at SF MOMA; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 3)
    - Disk Demo; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.10: Descent, 1.10
    - Descent; 1988 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:27:00:00 (Carton 39, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.11: Desire Inc., 1.11
    - [VHS Dub]; 1990 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:26:00:00 (Carton 35, Folder 1)
    - Edit; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.12: Double "Click" Face, 1.12
    - Double Click Face; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 18, Folder 1)
    - Multimedia Festival; 1995-04-23 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 2)
    - Dect. Office Pickup Scene, Embassy Exterior; 1994-04-22 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 3)
    - Embassy Lounge; 1995-04-22 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 4)
    - Embassy + Exteriors; 1995-04-22; 1995-04-23 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 5)
    - Exteriors + Sams Office; 1995-04-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 6)
    - Sams Office; 1995-04-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 7)
    - On-line Scenes; 1995-04-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 8)
    - On-line Scenes; 1995-04-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 9)
    - Sandy Stone B; 1995-04-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 10)
    - Sandy Stone A; 1995-04-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 11)
    - [Mias Camera Footage]; 1995-04-22; 1995-04-23 (10 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 18, Folder 12)
    - Music Double Face; 1980-06-05 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 18, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 1.13: Double Cross Click Click, 1.13
    - 1" Work Tape; 1995-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; [unidentified element]; 7 in. (Carton 17, Folder 2)
    - 1" Master; 1995-08-14 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 7 in. (Carton 17, Folder 3)
    - Veronica CP; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 4)
    - New Complete, [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 5)
    - ZPF, Guropea Backup, Backup [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 6)
    - Old BAVC Master; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min.; 00:28:00:00 (Carton 17, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 1.14: Double Speak, 1.14
    - Double Speak; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 43, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1.15: Double Take, 1.15
    - Double Take; 1998-10-14 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Sub Master; 30 min.; 00:24:30:00 (Carton 18, Folder 14)
    - Double Take; City Sites PSAs; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 9 in. (Carton 69, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.16: Duchamp Rough Cut, 1.16
    - Rough Cut of the Making of the Rough Cut - Marcel Duchamp; 1983-04-04 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min.; 00:13:00:00 (Carton 43, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 1.17: The Electronic Diaries of Lynn Hershman, 1.17
    - [Various Footage]; 1995-04 (2 items), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:75:00:00 (Carton 17, Folder 8)
    - The Electronic Diary; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 75 min. (Carton 34, Folder 1)
    - The Electronic Diary; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 34, Folder 2)
    - The Electronic Diary; 1989-1986 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 00:62:00:00 (Carton 34, Folder 3)
    - [Electronic Diaries various footage]; undated (13 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 34, Folder 4)
    - Electronic diary + Remote effects at end; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 30 min. (Carton 34, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1.18: Fine Cuts, 1.18
    - [Misc Audio Cassettes]; undated (44 items), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 28, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1.19: First Person Plural, 1.19
    - First Person Plural; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 36, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 1.20: Found Footage, 1.20
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element] (Carton 35, Folder 3)
    - Found Footage Titles; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 35, Folder 4)
    - Protection Realtime; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 5)
    - Seattle; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min., 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 6)
    - [unidentified]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min., 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 7)
    - adrian; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 5 min. (Carton 35, Folder 8)
    - Joana; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 35, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.21: Gaze, 1.21
    - Process, Prepare for Video Transfer; 1994-06-12 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 27, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.22: Hot Wire, 1.22
    - Film to Tape Transfer; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 35, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1.23: Information White Out, 1.23
    - Information Whiteout; 1987 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 18 min.; 00:12:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 7)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 36, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.24: Living Statues, 1.24
    - Music for Living Statues; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 30 min.; 00:20:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.25: Longshot, 1.25
    - Lian; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Soldier Story, not [illegible] shadow, [illegible]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - dennis voice over, lian as director; -10-19 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - [rmae art Pat a outer]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Lion Murder; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Lian Crying; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Aquatic Park; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master; 30 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot Final Version; 1989-05-11 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot; 1989-10-24 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:62:00:00 (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Longshot Final; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master; 60 min.; 00:60:00:00 (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - MOMA; 1990-05-04 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 13, Folder 13)
    - Mag for Kine Neg 1; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm Full Coat Magnetic; Soundtrack (Carton 14, Folder 1)
    - Kine Neg 1; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 14, Folder 2)
    - Mag for Kine Neg 2; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm Full Coat Magnetic; Soundtrack (Carton 14, Folder 3)
    - Kine Neg 2; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 14, Folder 4)
    - [various footage]; 1988 (8 items), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 1)
    - [unidentified]; 1993 (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 2)
    - Foot Steps; 1987 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 15, Folder 3)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 4)
    - George - Leanne; -07-21 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 5)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 6)
    - Dennis; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 7)
    - Lian; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 8)
    - [illegible] Lian; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 9)
    - S/O MO remote; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 10)
    - Rain - Zhu Zho, Lian; 1988-12-21 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 11)
    - [illegible] + George [illegible; 1989-01-01 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 12)
    - White pajamas/[illegible]; -11-09 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 13)
    - Lynn Dead, My V; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 14)
    - Lian, Mark Rennie; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 mins. (Carton 15, Folder 15)
    - First Date - Raw; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 mins. (Carton 15, Folder 16)
    - 6th Street; 1992-03-27 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 mins. (Carton 15, Folder 17)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 18)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 15, Folder 19)
    - Lian Flowers; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 16, Folder 1)
    - House of Flowers; 1988-02-07 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 16, Folder 2)
    - Lian I; 1988-04-05 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 16, Folder 3)
    - Lian Car; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 16, Folder 4)
    - Longshot Excerpt; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 16, Folder 5)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (6 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 16, Folder 6)
    - Longshot Final; 1989-11 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 9 in. (Carton 70, Folder 1)
    - Longshot; 1989-03-27 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 7 in. (Carton 70, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.26: Lorna, 1.26
    - [various footage]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 7)
    - Lorna Demo Master; 1985-08-15 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 18 min. (Carton 43, Folder 8)
    - Lorna Linear Master Edit; 1983 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 9)
    - [various footage]; undated (2 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 10)
    - [various footage]; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 43, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 1.27: Millenium Blues, 1.27
    - [Millenium Blues dubs]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 17, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.28: Nail Files, 1.28
    - Nail Files; 1997-01-31 (5 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 8)
    - Karen Black; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 9)
    - Roberta; 1997 (4 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 10)
    - [Nail Files various footage]; undated (4 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.29: Naked Eye, 1.29
    - Naked Eye Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 60 min. (Carton 17, Folder 10)
    - Naked Eye Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.30: Paranoid Mirror, 1.30
    - Mirror; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 5 min. (Carton 28, Folder 11)
    - [VHS Dub]; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 28, Folder 12)
    - [various footage]; undated (3 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 28, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 1.31: Peep Show, 1.31
    - Dub of Peep Show, Sig '93; 1993-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 36, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1.32: Prisoner of Paradise, 1.32
    - Prisoner of Paradise; 1984 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 7 min.; 00:07:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 11)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 36, Folder 12)
    - Prisoner Edit; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master; 18 min. (Carton 36, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 1.33: Questionable Behavior, 1.33
    - Rolls 1-2; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 27, Folder 5)
    - no audio recorded; 1993-12 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: 1/4" open reel; [unidentified element] (Carton 35, Folder 11)
    - [various footage]; undated (9 items), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 12)
    - 1&2; 1993-12 (1 item), Video: Hi8; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 35, Folder 13)
    - Film to Tape Transfer; 1993-12-15 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 14)
    - Transferred from Hi8, Take #1-2; 1993-12 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 35, Folder 15)
    - Questionable Credits, don carlos interviews; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 35, Folder 16)
    - Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 35, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1.34: Recovered Diaries, 1.34
    - Recovered Diaries; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; [unidentified element] (Carton 36, Folder 14)
    - [VHS Dub]; 1994 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 00:30:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 1.35: Remote Control, 1.35
    - Remote Control; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 12)
    - Remote Control Part II; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 60 min. (Carton 17, Folder 13)
    - Remote Control; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 30 min. (Carton 17, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 1.36: Roberta, 1.36
    - [Roberta footage]; 1997 (6 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 39, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1.37: Room of One's Own, 1.37
    - Room of One's Own; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 43, Folder 11)
    - Room of Her Own Final; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 43, Folder 12)
    - Demo; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:03:30:00 (Carton 43, Folder 13)
    - Room of Her Own installation; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 14)
    - Disk Room of her own; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 43, Folder 15)
    - Room of her own; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 43, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1.38: Seduction of a Cyborg, 1.38
    - Eyes & "LA Hi-8 Bump"; 1994-06-20 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min.; 00:60:00:00 (Carton 24, Folder 12)
    - 1. "Elle Est L.A.", 2. "Seduction of a Cyborg; 1994-07-05 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:14:00:00 (Carton 24, Folder 13)
    - Bumps; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 14)
    - Captured, Capp Street; 1994-06 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 15)
    - Captured + L.A., Capp Street; 1994-06 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 16)
    - LA, Capp Street; 1994-06 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 17)
    - L.A. Scene; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 24, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 1.39: Seeing Is Believing, 1.39
    - motorcycles + fight scene, Original; 1990-12-02 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Master (Carton 20, Folder 1)
    - BLK. BKRD - Estrella; 1991-03-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 20, Folder 2)
    - B-roll; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 10 min. (Carton 20, Folder 3)
    - Janet Orave #1, TOUR; 1990-08 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 20, Folder 4)
    - [illegible] Lynn Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 20, Folder 5)
    - Runaway; 1998-11-26 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 20, Folder 6)
    - Seeing is Believing Final; 1991 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 75 min. (Carton 20, Folder 7)
    - Motorcycle Footage, Original; 1990-12-02 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 20, Folder 8)
    - Edited Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 60 min. (Carton 20, Folder 9)
    - Master Second Section; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 20, Folder 10)
    - Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master (Carton 20, Folder 11)
    - [Seeing is Believing]; undated (17 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 20, Folder 12)
    - [VHS Dub]; 1991 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:72:00:00 (Carton 20, Folder 13)
    - Seeing is Believing; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Master; 7 in. (Carton 69, Folder 2)
    - Seeing is Believing; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Dub; 7 in. (Carton 69, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 1.40: Shadow's Song, 1.40
    - Shadow's Song; 1991 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min.; 00:33:00:00 (Carton 17, Folder 15)
    - Opening + X-Ray; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 17, Folder 16)